

# HAOWEI LI PhD Candidate

# DETAILS

lihw18@mails.tsinghua.edu.cn 17717366822

#### PROFILE

Ranked 1st in GPA from the second semester to the fourth, and won the National scholarship in 2020. One year experience in liquid metal laboratory and more than half year in medical imaging laboratory. During these periods, one Student Research Training (SRT) project have been finished on my own, while another Mixed-reality based SRT project is still on-going. Now working as a group leader in a running National College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Training Program.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Undergraduate, Tsinghua University, Beijing

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

- GPA 3.5, 4.0, 3.896, 3.867, 3.844 in past 5 semesters (full mark 4.0)
- Ranked 1st from the second semester to the fourth
- Won National scholarship in 2020
- Courses mainly focusing on medical imaging

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Medical Imaging laboratory, Prof. Guangzhi Wang

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- Half year attending group meeting and preparing software environment
- Learn to use unity and C# for Hololens development
- Registration of real world coordinate and Hololens coordinate basing on ArUco way and 3D point cloud
- Now working on the coding part of this project

#### National College Student Innovation and Entrepreneurship Training Program, Prof. Guoliang Huang

NOVEMBER 2020 — PRESENT

- Work as a leader in a national level financially supported project
- 3D skeleton fetched by Kinect or reconstructed from multi view 2D skeleton extracted by Alphapose
- Original classification with KNN and LSTM, now working on GCN based deep learning methods
- Datasets created and tagged on our own
- Now aiming to realize real time detection

## Liquid Metal laboratory, Prof. Jing Liu

OCTOBER 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020

 Half year doing experiments with senior students, familiar with preparation of magnetic liquid metal and relevant equipment

- SRT project established, recently published related articles were read for an overview, multiple versions of the article were written
- Strong covariance between magnetic field intensity and our material was observed, experiments were designed basing on this phenomena

## PUBLICATION

#### Co-author, A liquid gripper via phase transitional metallic ferrofluid

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Advanced Functional Materials in submission

## SKILLS

- Language: Chinese(Native); English(IELTS 7.5, CET6 612)
- Office Tools: Microsoft Office, Markdown, LaTeX
- Design Tools: AutoCAD, Unity, 3Dslicer, Magics, Meshmixer, Blender, Invesalius
- Engineering Tools: MATLAB, Multisim, Altium Designer
- Software Development: C++, C#, Python, Linux
- Hardware Development: Arduino, Hololens, Kinect

## SOCIAL ACTIVITIES

Minister, Sports department of the students' union of school of medical

AUGUST 2019 - JULY 2020

Team leader, Badminton team of school of medical

MARCH 2019 - DECEMBER 2020

## HONERS & AWARDS

- National Undergraduate Physics Competition (2019), Second Prize, Chinese Physics Society
- Scholarship for Sport Excellence(2019), Tsinghua University
- National Scholarship(2020), Ministry of Education of the People's Republic of China